我们好好的周二下午在这里干嘛
What the hell are we doing here on a Tuesday afternoon?
我们唯一的顾客是厄尔
The only customer we had was Earl
他忘了自己在这里工作 还跟我们点了午餐
and he forgot he works here and ordered lunch.
首先 你忘了那群溜了进来
First of all, you are forgetting the pack of dogs
在我们店里大杂交一番就跑掉的野狗
that wandered in, had an orgy, and left.
我这么容易就忘掉这件事
Probably easy for me to forget 'cause
大概是因为它们想搞的对象不是我
I wasn't the one they tried to have sex with.
其次 我们还在这里工作的原因是因为
And we still have to work here because our dessert bar's
甜品酒吧才开一周 我们需要这笔收入
only been open a week; we need income.
我不喜欢白天上班
I don't like working in the daytime.
明亮的光线会让你看见一堆奇怪事物
You can see freaky things in this light.
你看有只蚂蚁在搬凳子[屎]
Look, there's an ant carrying a stool.
看啊 有个屁都不搬的服务员
Look, there's a waitress carrying nothing.
阿憨 你居然有钱买新凳子
Wow, Han, you have new-stool money?
你上了福布斯"40以下4尺男"排行吗
Are you in Forbes' "40 Under 4 Feet?"
不是我买的 是幸运女神的赏赐
I didn't buy this. Lady Luck threw me a bone.
我敢肯定她早上醒来一定恨死自己
I'm sure she hated herself in the morning.
我们楼里一名受人敬爱的长者去世了
A beloved old man in my building passed away,
在街坊邻居们都献上哀悼之意后
and after the neighbors paid our solemn respects,
我们搬空了他家
we cleaned the dump out.
阿憨 这也太大不敬了吧
Han, that is so disrespectful.
我们怎么没收到短信通知
We didn't get a text?
差点忘了我抢到的甜甜圈形痔疮坐垫
Ooh, I forgot my sweet hemorrhoid doughnut I scored.
无论有没有痔疮都能享用
You don't need hemorrhoids to enjoy it.
甜甜圈形痔疮坐垫
Hemorrhoid doughnut.
不含卡路里 舒适到心底
All of the comfort and none of the calories.
新凳子啊
Ooh! A new stool.
2005年感觉是丰收的一年啊
2005 is shaping up to be a great year.
那是阿憨的凳子
That's Han's stool.
阿憨的凳子刚买了一张
Well, Han's stool just bought
直达厄尔屁股的有去无回票
a one-way ticket to Earl's butt.
这真是我看过最凄凉的一集
This the saddest episode of Game of Thrones
"权凳的游戏"
I've ever seen.
不过我还是支持矮人
Still, I'm rooting for the dwarf.
今晚我们要出征威廉斯堡最潮之处
Tonight, we are hitting the chic-est spot in Williamsburg
去抢他们最潮的客人
to poach their chic-est patrons.
如果基础客户能建立在
If we start out with a cool clientele,
模特 男同性恋
models, gays,
还有想搞模特跟男同的有钱人上
rich guys that want to have sex with models and gays,
起码未来五年我们都会是炙手可热的潮店
we'll be an in-spot for at least five years.
你刚才是在跟我说话啊
Were you talking to me that whole time?
不然我还能是在跟谁说
Who else would I be talking to?
这里只有你一个人
You're the only one here.
你那个是兰迪花痴笑
That was a Randy giggle.
而这个是兰迪的大雕
And that's Randy's penis.
不是全景 这屏幕挺小的
Not all of it. It's a pretty small screen.
我们决定继续我们的开放恋爱式的
Yeah, we decided to continue our nonexclusive,
远距离性爱短信
long-distance, sexting thing.
这个是牛津英语词典上的解释吗
Is that the Oxford English Dictionary definition?
如果牛津也喜欢光身在手机上做深蹲那就是
If Oxford likes to get naked and squat over a phone.
但你的姐妹就要想不出性爱短信内容啦
But your girl's running out of sexting ideas.
只有四个表情符号看起来像阴茎
There's only four emojis that look like penises.
算上连皮玉米那个符号 那就五个
Five if you count the corn on the cob.
拜托别毁连皮玉米符号在我心中形象
Don't ruin the corn on the cob for me.
我用它来表示烧烤会跟农贸市场
I use that for barbecues and farmers markets.
原来你之前说的是这意思啊
That's what you were talking about?
我现在就把所有话都加上"我裤裆里的"
I've just been adding "in my pants" to everything.
比如说
Example:
"你觉得我裤裆里的
"What do you think about climate change
气候变化怎么样"
in my pants?"
拜托你 我需要你今晚集中注意力
Come on, I need you focused tonight.
别发性爱短信了
No more sexting.
把手机扔一边去 让他也这样
Just put it away and tell him to do the same.
好了 让我找找茄子的表情符号
All right, let me just find the eggplant emoji
还有裤子的符号
and, of course, the pants.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
苏菲 你需要帮忙吗...
Oh, do you need a hand there, Soph...
我能行
I can do it!
苏菲 为什么要推超大台老式婴儿车
Sophie, why the enormous old-timey stroller?
这豪气座驾里最好有个
There better be a cartoon baby
穿得像传奇黑帮大哥的卡通婴儿
dressed like Al Capone in that thing.
两位
Hey, girls,
我今晚能跟芭芭拉在你家暂住一晚吗
can Barbara and me stay down here tonight?
我跟奥列格还得再等两周才能做爱
Oleg and I can't have sex for two more weeks
楼上干柴烈火一点就要着了
and it's just getting too steamy up there.
难怪我们能从四面八方
So, that explains the heavy panting
屋顶 墙壁 还有最恶心人的
we're hearing through our ceiling, our walls, and
排水口听到喘息声
most disturbing of all, our drain.
我想去嘘嘘
I gotta pee.
我现在无时无刻想嘘嘘
I gotta go all the time now.
有件事我得告诉你们俩
You know, that's something that you girls need to know about me.
每次我们说话
Any time that we talk,
我都会漏两滴
I'm peeing a little bit.
哎 爽
Uh... yeah.
看看爸爸的小拦"鸡"虎
There's daddy's little jock block.
我尝试用创意的方式舒缓我房事不如意
I tried to release my sexual frustration creatively,
但我投稿的情色诗歌
but my erotic poetry
被《国家"弟立"》杂志拒绝了
was rejected by National Pornographic
理由是"下流恶心"
for being, quote, "Just disgusting."
我的性爱短信就苍白无力
My sexts are so lame.
为什么我就做不到下流恶心
Why can't I be disgusting?
你的梳妆台侧边还卡着一个墨西哥卷饼
There's a burrito stuck to the side of your dresser.
你绝对够恶心
You're there.
"等不及在我裤裆里把
"Can't wait for you to put your butt
你的屁股放到
on top of... my butt
我的屁股上"
in my pants"?
我去 谢谢你让我的淫虫全尴尬至死
Jeez, thanks for the nice break from being horny.
性爱短信不够污 我也很苦恼啊
I am not proud of how not slutty it is.
快把我的手机还我 它还没打过性病疫苗
Now, give me back my phone. It hasn't had its shots.
-已发送 -什么
- Sent. - What?
"你的蛋蛋就像两颗闪耀的巧克力蛋
"Your testicles are two glistening Cadbury Eggs,
而老娘最爱吃甜食了"
and Mama's got a sweet tooth."
而老娘现在超级想吐
This mama's got puke in her mouth.
我真不敢相信你会发这么恶心的东西
I cannot believe you'd send something so disgusting.
我恨死...
You are dead to m...
他喜欢
He likes it!
想把男人撩得欲火焚身吗
You want to turn a man on?
请致电奥列格
Heh, you call Oleg.
希望不会让你太吃醋 不过...
I hope it doesn't make you too jealous, but
我刚才跟兰迪发了性爱短信呢
I was just sexting with Randy.
是吗
Yeah?
卡洛琳 去拿水管
Caroline, get the hose.
记住 我们目标是模特 男同性恋
Okay, now remember, we're targeting models, gays,
还有钱多没处花的富二代
and upwardly mobile millennials with discretionary income.
基本上比我们强的任何人都行
Basically anyone better than us.
你刚才又都是在跟我说话了吗
Were you talking to me that whole time?
是的 我刚才都是在跟你说话
And yes, I was talking to you that whole time.
请出示证件
IDs, please?
你知道他们不会逼你一定要用
You know they don't force you to use
拍出来的第一张照吧
the first picture they take.
我的证件照里我在吃腌瓜
I'm eating a pickle in mine.
我觉得你看起来很好啊
I think you look great.
你好 我叫杰克
Hi, I'm Jake.
你好啊 杰克
Hi, Jake.
杰克 证件
ID, Jake?
他大概27岁
He's about 27,
能自由花用的收入挺多
lots of discresh income?
正是27岁
27 exactly.
猜对我的体重 我就请你喝酒
Guess my weight and I'll buy you a drink.
你们是如何保持没有白痴客人的环境
So, um, how do you maintain such a dork-less clientele?
我有个智障室友方面的问题
I need to know 'cause I have a roommate situation.
看着学吧 腌瓜妹
Watch and learn, pickles.
赞啊
Oh, sweet,
卡通《神偷卡门》的卡门来了
I found Carmen Sandiego.
我不知道你这次想闯进哪里
I don't know where in the world you're going, buddy,
但这里你是别想了
but it ain't in here.
这里有你搞定
Oh, you got this.
但千万别让那个背带裤男走掉
But do not let the guy in the overalls
得等我叫完他"哈欠小农"才能放他走
get out of here without me calling him "Farmer Yawn."
麦克斯 我简直是如鱼得水啊
Max, I am killing it.
你刚才见过杰克了
Jake, you've met.
娜哈尼跟艾瑞儿都是模特
Nahani and Ariel are models.
她们吃啥都不会胖
They can eat whatever they want.
羡慕嫉妒恨啊
Hate them.
而这两位是泰德与詹姆森 是同性恋
And then, this is Tad and Jameson, they're gay.
我透过芭比娃娃
I perform reenactments
来演绎女歌手艾米·怀恩豪斯她悲剧的一生
of the life and tragic death of Amy Winehouse with Barbies.
我在文具店工作
I work at Staples.
权力夫夫啊
Oh, power couple.
纽约的精英界人士 除了我 都不在此
None of New York's elite are here, besides me.
看来我是不够格去芭比·怀恩豪斯秀的后台了
I guess I'm not going backstage at Barbie Winehouse.
你试着邀请他们来酒吧
You tried to make them come to this bar
而他们说"不要 不要 不要"
and they said, "No, no, no."
我的基佬们在12点钟方向
My gay guys at 12:00.
我话说太早了
I spoke too soon.
你还喷了点口水
And you spat a little.
泰德 詹姆森
Tad! Jameson!
欢迎来到麦与卡的甜品酒吧
Welcome to the M and C Dessert Bar.
不 你不是在做梦
No, you're not dreaming!
他们如果是在做梦 我俩会是上空裸男
If they were, we'd be shirtless dudes.
这里赞赞哒
This place is fabulous.
我能点一杯这个饼干面团丁尼吗
Can I have one of these cookie dough-tinis?
今晚是我的出轨夜
It's my cheat night,
所以我才跟他来
that's why I'm with him.
我不知道这些女壮士哪来的
Hmm, not sure who these gals are.
麦克斯 你在修车厂提起过我们店吗
Max, did you talk about this place at Pep Boys?
我跟曼尼还有摩尔说了
I told Manny and Moe,
但我绝对没跟杰克提
but I didn't say a word to Jack.
泰德 让我再给你续一杯
Oh, Tad. Let me get you another one.
没事 没事
It's fine, it's fine.
-真的没事吗 -有事
- It is? - No.
"没事没事"就是基佬语的"我们要走了"
That's gay for "We're leaving."
她们把我的帅男同们吓跑了
They chased off my hot gay guys.
我不想无礼
I don't want to be rude here,
但是谁邀请这些女汉子的
but who invited these horrible women?
夏琳驾到
Charlene's in the house!
凶手来了 我去 麦克斯
And there it is. Damn it, Max.
你为什么要邀请你的门卫朋友来啊
Why did you invite your bouncer buddy
你明知道我想营造个高档客群环境
when you know I'm trying to cultivate a vibe?
我没邀请她啊
I didn't invite her.
我也不知道她会穿运动短裤
And I did not think she'd be wearing gym shorts
跟纽约州立大学奥尔巴尼分校的卫衣啊
and a SUNY Albany sweatshirt.
我知道你们想要邀请很屌的客人来
Hey, I know you guys were trying to get the cool crowd in here,
所以 不用谢啦
so, you know,
屌炸
boom!
所以你说的很屌的客人们都在哪
And where are they? The cool people?
好啦 放轻松
All right. Take it easy.
说不定人家都很屌呢
Maybe they are cool.
那个人在吃花生果酱三明治吗
Is that one eating a PB and J?
好啦
All right!
谁想来跟大瑞芭比比
Who wants to take on Big Reba?
怎么比比
Take on how?
麦克斯 你会流氓语
Max, you speak Goon.
怎么 怎么比啊
How? How... how?
我流氓语水平不佳啊
Not fluently.
我只在流氓市住过一学期
I only lived in Goon for a semester.
那来挑呗
You're on.
怎么挑啊
On how?
怎么 是要怎么挑
How... how?
太好了 她们还带了绳子
Oh good, they brought rope.
希望她们有多带一点让我上吊
I hope they brought some for me too.
可她们没带腋下除臭剂
And they did not bring deodorant.
女士们 这是闹哪样
Ladies, what is this
怎么样才能让你们停下呢
and how can we make it stop?
你们得到机会前排近距离观赏
You got a front row seat to New York City's elite
纽约精英级地下女子掰腕子大赛
underground ladies' arm wrestling.
一 二 三
One, two, three,
开掰
wrestle!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我拥有一间掰腕子酒吧
I own an arm wrestling bar.
你才没有
No, you don't.
是我们拥有一家掰腕子俱乐部
We own an arm wrestling bar!
希望你是在发短信给夏琳
I hope you're texting Charlene
跟她的"职业手腕摔跤"同伴们
and the rest of her WWE Raw crowd
别再回来我们店
to never come back to our bar.
你一边哭哭啼啼一边跪求她们停下
Uh, you were sobbing and begging them to stop.
我想她应该知道你意思了
I think she got the message.
我不知道她有没有听进去啊
I don't know if she was listening.
她当时忙着把大瑞芭扛在肩膀上绕场
She was carrying Big Reba around on her shoulders.
这也太凄凉了吧
This is pitiful.
我刚拿企鹅照片当性爱短信发给了兰迪
I just sexted Randy a picture of a penguin.
我压根都不觉得企鹅性感
I don't even think penguins are that sexy!
老天 我现在看见啥都想上
Oh, my God. Everything is turning me on.
我刚看见洗手间里有一位老太太
I just walked in on an elderly lady in the bathroom
我差点没控制住
and almost lost my mind.
你去女厕所干嘛
What were you doing in the ladies' room?
好啦 其实那是个老头
All right, fine, it was a man.
得了 每个人都有自己的烦恼
Yeah, we all have problems.
我有性爱短信创作瓶颈
I have sexter's block.
要我帮你试[湿]一下吗
Want me to take a stab at it?
瞧 随便一句都能秒杀我
See, that's already better than anything I have.
写下来就行
Just write it down.
我可不想我的手机沾上你的指纹
I don't want your fingerprints on my phone.
你觉得我还没弄掉手指指纹吗
You think I still have fingerprints?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你真的要跟奥列格做爱了吗
Are you really gonna have sext with Oleg?
我不知道你为什么觉得我不会
I don't know why you think I'm above this.
让开 厄尔在到处找我
Out of the way. Earl's looking for me.
一旦他反应过来自己在外面
And as soon as he realizes he's outside,
我就有大麻烦了
I'm in big trouble.
人能取关现实生活中的人吗
Can you unfollow a person in real life?
我该把这凳子藏哪里 他会完全猜不到呢
Where would he least expect me to hide this?
高处吗
Up high?
"小短腿爬不高" 厄尔肯定会这么说
"Shorty wouldn't go high," Earl would say.
那可不一定哦 厄尔
Oh, won't I, Earl?
阿憨 你在自言自语
Han, you're talking to yourself.
你干嘛不直接再买一把就好啦
And why don't you just buy another stool?
厄尔要的是这把
Earl wants this one.
这一次 他绝不能如愿以偿
And for once in his life, he's not gonna get what he wants!
我把凳子藏下面 等他忘了这事就好了
I'll just keep it under here till he forgets about it.
大概一个小时后就能忘得差不多
Which should be in about an hour.
昨天我看见他往自己三明治上放硬币
Yesterday I caught him putting pennies on his sandwich.
来玩我藏你找啊 老家伙
Hide and seek, old timer.
我不知道他怎么有办法
I don't know how it's possible,
不断超越怪的极限
but he's getting weirder.
那些掰腕子的人今晚不会来了吧 麦克斯
Those wrestlers won't be back tonight, right, Max?
对不对 上帝 您在吗 上帝
Right, God? Are you there, God?
我是卡洛琳 一名被您遗忘的女子
It's me, Caroline, the one you forgot about?
那个龟孙把老子的凳子藏哪儿了
Where'd that turd hide my stool?
谢谢各位
Thanks, y'all.
我就知道小短腿爬不高
I knew Shorty wouldn't go high.
奥列格 写得怎么样了
Oleg, how you doing over there?
你需要一份更大流量的手机套餐
You're gonna need a bigger data plan.
麦克斯 已经连续两晚了
Max, it's been two nights in a row.
如果我们不防微杜渐
If we don't nip this in the bud,
就会沦落为掰腕子大力女的小女友了
we're both gonna be lady arm wrestlers' girlfriends.
就算你不是
You're not exactly thriving
掰腕子大力女的小女友 情况也没多好啊
not being a lady arm wrestler's girlfriend.
我不懂这有什么问题
And I don't see what the problem is.
她们都是来消费的顾客
They're paying customers.
她们有在喝啤酒啊
They're drinking beer.
啤酒头盔里的酒是她们自带的
From a helmet they brought with them.
不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
别走啊 请留步 先生
Don't go, don't go. Please, please, sir.
我们酒吧仅存的安慰走了
Well, the last of our vibe is leaving.
我敢说那些女人都有自慰棒
Pretty sure all these ladies have vibes.
应该是老式带插头的那种
Guessing vintage plug-ins.
真是够了
That's it.
各位
Everybody!
你们不能再来这里玩掰腕子游戏了
You cannot have your arm wrestling meetings here anymore.
找个码头 废车场
Find a dock or a junkyard
或找间体育酒吧
or a Buffalo Wild Wings.
谁想在上班的地方喝酒啊
Who wants to drink where they work?
-就是 -没错
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你这是赤裸裸的歧视
This is discrimination.
-就是 -没错
- Yeah! - Yeah.
女士 我可以超级支持女同性恋的哟
Look, miss, I am extremely pro-lesbian.
请告诉我你们是拉拉
Please be lesbians.
我们不是拉拉
We're not lesbians.
哎哟哟 挥棒落空
Ooh, swing and a miss.
其实我是
Actually, I am.
这是我第一次大声说出来 对吧
That's the first time I've said that out loud, isn't it?
如释重负
Wow, that's freeing.
我只是反对在我的甜品酒吧掰腕子
I am just anti-arm wrestling in my dessert bar.
好硬气的小咪咪
Well, tough ta-tas.
我另一个绰号正好叫硬咪咪
Which happens to be my other nickname.
来啊 试一下
Go ahead, take a shot.
算了吧
I'll pass.
等等
Hold on, um,
是不是谁都可以打咪咪拳
is that an open offer on the, uh, ta-ta punch?
你们至少能点几杯喝的吗
Will you at least order some drinks?
好吧 我们点
Okay, we'll order
12杯水
12 waters.
免费自来水哦
Tap.
各位 拜托 这是我的梦想
You guys, please, this is my dream.
我的梦想里没有汽水污渍的运动裤
And my dream doesn't have soda-stained sweatpants in it.
那污渍来自果冻 不过随便啦
It's jelly, but whatever.
我是一个讲理的女人
I'm a reasonable woman.
没错 她说得对
Yes, that is true.
她比火车站的大瑞芭讲理多了
She's more reasonable than the Big Reba at the train station.
没问题 我们可以走
Fine, we'll leave.
前提是你们俩有一个能在掰腕子中赢我们
If one of you can beat me arm wrestling.
但如果你们俩都不能
But if neither of you can,
那我和我的人就不走了
my squad and I stay.
上世纪80年代帮派老片的即视感
Getting real '80s movie up in here.
如何 谁上啊
Huh? Who's it gonna be?
肯定是你啊 麦克斯
It has to be you, Max.
我弱不禁风 楚楚动人 闭月羞花
I'm weak, fragile, beautiful,
同时还平易近人
but approachable.
准备好让姐姐给你上一课了吗 奶妹
Ready to get taught a lesson there, Jugsy?
给你上一课的时间到了 小芭芭
School's in session, Reebs.
但还是叫我麦克斯吧
But call me Max.
奶妹是我妈的名字
Jugsy is my mother's name.
加油 麦克斯
Do it, Max.
她会把你打趴下
She is gonna take you down
下到十八层地狱
to downtown...
开着小车下去
In a car,
而那辆车名叫
made of...
痛苦
pain.
乖乖观战少废话
Maybe just watch.
听我数到三 一 二 三 开掰
On my count. One, two, three, wrestle!
手腕撑不住了 精力全用完了
Wrist can't hold! Nothing in the tank!
性爱短信把我掏空了
All the sexting!
上啊 麦克斯 挺起腰杆再拼一把
Fight, Max! Put your back into it!
我的腰杆也不行了啊
My back's shot too.
没看到我胸口的两大负重袋吗
Haven't you seen my front?
姐们不走了
We're staying, girls!
麦克斯 我们该怎么办
Max, what are we gonna do?
下一步显而易见
I think it's pretty clear.
你得跟大瑞芭掰腕子
You're gonna have to arm wrestle Big Reba.
我不能直接嫁给她吗
Can't I just marry her?
加油 卡洛琳 你能行的
Come on now, Caroline, you got this.
这么多年来你一直跟失望抗争
You've been wrestling with disappointment for years.
而我节节败退
And I'm losing.
听我数到三
On my count.
一 二 三
One, two, three,
开掰
wrestle!
你们看见我的凳子了吗
Ya'll seen the stool?
阿憨又藏起来了
Han hid it again.
我的乖乖 你们到底在干什么
What in the sweet name of Jesus is going on in here?
厄尔 我在努力激励卡洛琳
Earl, I'm trying to motivate Caroline.
你记得《洛奇》里面的任何一句台词吗
Do you remember any of the lines from Rocky?
我用我一天跟游客说三次的那句话回答你
I'm gonna tell you what I tell three tourists a day.
我不是卡尔·韦瑟斯
I am not Carl Weathers.
麦克斯 我要输了
Max, I'm losing it!
-快帮帮那可怜的姑娘 -卡洛琳
- Help that poor girl. - Uh, Caroline,
瞧瞧这些掰腕子大力女
look at all these arm wrestling ladies
在你梦想的甜品酒吧里
in your dream dessert bar!
五年来你一直梦想重回上流社会
You were aiming for five years of class,
但你连一个小时都不曾拥有
you didn't even get an hour!
我的婴儿推车进不去你们的甜品酒吧
Hey, I can't get the carriage in the dessert bar!
唯一能推进去的地方就是洗车处
The only place it would fit was the car wash.
这是怎么回事
Hey, what is all this?
卡洛琳在奋力赢回我们的酒吧
Caroline is trying win our bar back,
而我在努力激励她
and I'm trying to inspire her
方式就是指出她的人生有多惨
by pointing out how bad her life is.
居然没人发短信通知我吗
And I didn't get a text?
麦克斯 帮帮忙
Max, help!
你都一年没做过爱了
Uh... you haven't had sex in a year!
我想你应该懂 我说一年已经很厚道了
And I think you know I'm being quite generous there.
奏效了 她空虚寂寞冷
It's working. She's lonely.
你为了捡一块钱追到了地铁的铁轨上
You chased a dollar onto the third rail of the subway,
最后还没有捡到
and you didn't get it!
你在一家餐厅当服务员
You work as a waitress in a diner!
你有没有提服务员的事
Did you mention the waitress thing?
我刚提了 厄尔
Yes, I just did, Earl.
抱歉 我脑子反应有点缓慢
Sorry, things are getting to me a little late.
等等 你有告诉她我宝宝芭芭拉
Wait, did... did you tell her that baby Barbara
会比她还早结婚吗
is gonna get married before she is?
卡洛琳
Caroline,
六年前
six years ago,
你家财万贯
you had a billion dollars,
而现在 这话我一定要说
and now... I'm gonna say it...
说啊
Say it!
班尼路你都买不起
Old Navy is out of your price range!
兰迪一直没回我短信
I haven't heard from Randy.
奥列格的图文性爱短信肯定把他吓着了
Oleg's graphic sexts must've freaked him out.
我发最后一条的时候连Siri都把眼睛挡上了
Even Siri covered her eyes after that last one I sent.
你让米开朗基罗作画
You ask Michelangelo to paint,
画完之后你又嫌东嫌西
and then you criticize the painting.
你干嘛把忍者神龟扯进来
Why are you bringing the Ninja Turtles into this?
我只是想知道现在该怎么办
I just want to know what to do now.
我完全理解你不会想听
I completely understand if you don't
来自掰腕子冠军的爱情建议
want to take love advice from an arm wrestling champion,
但何不简单地问声好或说"我想你"呢
but why don't you just say "Hi" Or "I miss you"?
"你好 我想你"
"Hi, I miss you"?
前面不加上"我裤裆里"吗
No "in my pants"?
好吧 那我试试
Okay, fine. I'll give it a shot.
大家安...
Hey everyb...
靠
Damn it.
你需要帮忙吗 苏菲
Do you need a hand there, Sophie?
不必 我能行
No, I got it!
很明显你不需要帮忙
You really don't.
厄尔 凳子给你吧
Earl, you can have the stool.
我今年过得很不顺
I've had a really hard year,
我允许自己就放纵这么一次
and I allowed myself this one indulgence.
但如果真这么重要...
But, if it's important...
好 那我就收下啦
Sweet, I'll take it.
冷酷无情
Oof! Cold as ice.
我又不是来这交朋友的
I didn't come here to make friends.
凳子不给你了
No stool for you.
二位 我们何不用
Hey... hey, why don't we settle this
80年代老片的方式 用臂力一决胜负
the 80s movie way and arm muscle for it?
以我现在的年纪 唯一能欺负的就只有小女孩了
At my age, only thing I can beat is a little girl.
所以没问题
So, yeah.
开战吧
Bring it on.
这位小女孩 可比外表看起来强壮多了
This little girl's tougher than she looks.
等我冲你的屁股一顿暴打后
You won't be able to sit on that damn thing
那把破凳子你想坐都坐不了 小短腿
after the ass whooping I'm about to lay on you, Shorty.
小短腿的屁股承受力可强了呢 老家伙
Shorty's ass can take a lot, old man!
阿憨 你的性事我们不想知道
We don't want to hear about your personal life, Han.
一 二 三 开掰
One, two, three, wrestle!
他们开始了吗
Have they started yet?
等完事后
When this is over,
我肯定会精疲力尽
I'm gonna be wiped out.
你会帮我把凳子抬回去吗
You gonna help me carry my stool back up there?
我有个主意
Here's an idea.
快说啊 阿憨
Yeah, you say it, Han!
下地狱吧
Burn in hell!
还记得以前我也让你这么呻吟吗
Remember when I used to make you moan like that?
你真是让我欲火焚身
You really turn me on.
芭芭拉 你跟爸比待着
Barbara, you stay with your daddy.
他是一个超级性感的男人
He's a very sexy man.
兰迪回我短信了 说"我想你"
Randy texted me back "I miss you."
真有爱
Aw, that's so sweet.
是他的裤裆里在想我
Oh! In his pants!
靠 阿憨
Damn, Han,
我没想到口臭是你的秘密武器
I didn't realize bad breath was your secret weapon.
被坑了吧 小短腿
Stool me, Shorty.
谁想跟我掰腕子争甜甜圈形痔疮垫呀
Who am I wrestling for the hemorrhoid doughnut?